# Mohith Sarvepalli

#### Student

As an experienced SWE, I bring a unique blend of technical skills and problem-solving abilities to any team. With a track record of successfully designing and implementing highly available and scalable projects, I am confident in my ability to contribute to any project. Let's build something great together!

mohithsarvepalli@gmail.com

9100433243

Nellore, India

# mohithsarvepalli.com

### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor of Technology(CSE) Vellore Institute of Technology

07/2018 - 05/2022

Passwd with CGPA-8 73/10

#### Intermediate

Narayana Group of Institutions

06/2016 - 05/2018

Passed with 953/1000

### Class 10th

Narayana Group of Institutions

06/2015 - 05/2016

Passed with 9.7/10

## **COURSE PROJECTS**

#### Online Exam Portal

- Portal for teachers to create and configure, and students to attempt online exams.
- Front end using HTML, CSS and JavaScript for styling.
- Back end: php and MYSQL.

#### 3D RPG Game using unity

- Used unity assets for the characters and animations.
- Used C# for executing the commands and control.

#### Detecting of e-Phishing sites

- Used the Link Guard Algorithm to find the phishing electronic message.
- Handles 5 categories of phishing.

#### Secure Storage Using Cryptography

 Used both symmetric encryption(DES) and asymmetric encryption(RSA) for securing the message.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **SWE-I Engineer**

NCR Corporation 07/2022 - Present

- Working as Site Reliability Engineer

- Working with google cloud platform in maintaining infrastructure.
- Played a key role in trouble shooting and fixing the infrastructure.
- Punctual with work.

## **Lead App Developer**

Monktree Education Pvt Ltd

06/2020 - 08/2020

Worked on developing a Dating Mobile App

Achievements/Tasks

- Done with frontend part for the application.
- Took the responsibilty of team.
- Punctual with work.

## **SKILLS**



## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Member of NSS VIT, 2019-2020

Secured All India rank 2081 in final round of 5th International Maths Olympiad.

Secured All India Rank 251 in National Level Science Talent Search Examination

Secured All India Rank 109 in final round of 15th National Science Olympiad

Lead a Cricket Team into finals in Inter-School Championship.

## **CERTIFICATES**

Using JavaScript ,JQuery and JSON in Django

Udemy Java Programming Masterclass 🗹

Frontend Fundamentals 🗹

Building Arduino Robots and Devices

Unity Environment Design 🗹

Terraform for Beginners using GCP - Google Cloud

#### INTERESTS

